This is a demo video of how to make an iDubbbz
First, turn on the admin to access the iDubbbz tool
Then, open tuner cache
Open tuner cache
After that, we will import the database from TCM
This is the database from TCM
We will get the name of the item and find it in the component name
After finding the item, check if the version is correct
Then create an ITT
Create a test environment for the item
This is a test environment for the item
Create an ITT item for Atom
Find missing parameters
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching and see you next time!
Find the missing formulas after adding the parameters
Import the formulas that have been exported
After completing the step of creating an ITT item
Next, we will use the Align tool to create a test design
Pay attention to this
Next is the Preset tool
This tool will display the number of values according to the loweruka
Then we will use the Line tool
Create the required files in the ITT section of ITEM
to be able to use GenTestDesign
Thanks for watching and see you next time
After that, enter the required information in the Alino tool to be able to use GenTestDesign
The name of the module, the version, the number of characters, the item to create the module, where to store GenTestDesign
After that, import the .dcm file
For GenTestDesign
Go to GenTestDesign
After that, go to Xport
After that, copy the correct information in the class
and add them to the .dcm file
Then, we will use the local parameters to check the min and max tolerance of the inputs.
Please subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Thanks for watching
Subscribe to La La School channel to not miss the fascinating videos
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Check the local parameters
Password you enter
Go ahead and write the formula for the return value variable.
Then press Generate Test Case.
To start the test, click Generate Test Case.
The test design has been created successfully.
After creating the test design, we will create the test case to cover the second test case.
The new rebate of this test only requires C0C1, so we will only create the test case to cover C0C1.
This is the main information tab of the class, including the review source, testers, and the percentage of C0C1 MCDC of the class.
Next, we will proceed to the step of importing the test case.
Import the test case.
Next, we will import the test case into the test design in the ATT department.
We will selectных the part name and promoteпарm.
We will use the Smart ATT tool to import the test case into the ATT department.
We will choose the tools selected.
Enter the required information into the tool to be able to type the test case.
The test case is ready.
You may begin the test.
Please touch the work.
The test has been completed.
Please be careful.
Please be careful when using the test.
The test is ready.
End of the test.
After that, we will run the test to see the result of the test.
As you can see, the item has been full 100%
These are the test cases that have been added from testdesign into ITT
Thank you for watching
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
This is the result of the display of the % of V001
Thank you for watching
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
ativa
After creating the VOT, we will proceed to the transformation.
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
After creating the VOT, we will proceed to the TCM.
Because this item does not require MCDC, we will select a region for the conditions that need to be MCDC
MCDC does not require
Subtitles by the Amara.org community
Enter the necessary schools in the MCTC tool to create a workroom.
け
Well done.
Thank you!
After that, we will create a new rule for the item
Next step is to get the link on TCM
Click on the link to get the link
Now we will create a new rule for the item
Then click on the link to get the link
Subtitles by the Amara.org community